<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<data>
    <topic name="koira">
        <note name="koira">
            <text>124</text>
            <timestamp>11.03.2025 13:24</timestamp>
        </note>
        <note name="koira">
            <text>saklgsfb</text>
            <timestamp>11.03.2025 13:26</timestamp>
        </note>
    </topic>
    <topic name="Koira">
        <note name="Koira">
            <text>Koira is a Town, Block and tahsil in Sundargarh District, Odisha, India.</text>
            <timestamp>11.03.2025 14:07</timestamp>
        </note>
        <note name="Koira">
            <text>Yllä oleva ei oo totta lol</text>
            <timestamp>11.03.2025 14:17</timestamp>
        </note>
        <note name="Koira">
            <text>Koira is a Town, Block and tahsil in Sundargarh District, Odisha, India.</text>
            <timestamp>11.03.2025 14:17</timestamp>
        </note>
    <note name="Koira"><text>Koira is a Town, Block and tahsil  in Sundargarh District, Odisha, India.</text><timestamp>13.03.2025 20:23</timestamp></note></topic>
    <topic name="Viina">
        <note name="Viina">
            <text>koira</text>
            <timestamp>11.03.2025 14:21</timestamp>
        </note>
    </topic>
<topic name="Linux"><note name="Linux"><text>Linux (, LIN-uuks) is a family of open-source Unix-like operating systems based on the Linux kernel, an operating system kernel first released on September 17, 1991, by Linus Torvalds. Linux is typically packaged as a Linux distribution (distro), which includes the kernel and supporting system software and libraries—most of which are provided by third parties—to create a complete operating system, designed as a clone of Unix and released under the copyleft GPL license.
Thousands of Linux distributions exist, many based directly or indirectly on other distributions; popular Linux distributions include Debian, Fedora Linux, Linux Mint, Arch Linux, and Ubuntu, while commercial distributions include Red Hat Enterprise Linux, SUSE Linux Enterprise, and ChromeOS. Linux distributions are frequently used in server platforms. Many Linux distributions use the word "Linux" in their name, but the Free Software Foundation uses and recommends the name "GNU/Linux" to emphasize the use and importance of GNU software in many distributions, causing some controversy. Other than the Linux kernel, key components that make up a distribution may include a display server (windowing system), a package manager, a bootloader and a Unix shell.

Linux is one of the most prominent examples of free and open-source software collaboration. While originally developed for x86 based personal computers, it has since been ported to more platforms than any other operating system, and is used on a wide variety of devices including PCs, workstations, mainframes and embedded systems. Linux is the predominant operating system for servers and is also used on all of the world's 500 fastest supercomputers. When combined with Android, which is Linux-based and designed for smartphones, they have the largest installed base of all general-purpose operating systems.</text><timestamp>13.03.2025 20:14</timestamp></note></topic><topic name="Hampi"><note name="Hampi"><text>Hampi or Hampe (Kannada: [hɐmpe]), also referred to as the Group of Monuments at Hampi, is a UNESCO World Heritage Site located in the town of Hampi in Vijayanagara district, east-central Karnataka, India. Hampi predates the Vijayanagara Empire; it is mentioned in the Ramayana and the Puranas of Hinduism as Pampa Devi Tirtha Kshetra. Hampi continues as a religious centre, with the Virupaksha Temple, an active Adi Shankara-linked monastery and various monuments belonging to the old city.
Hampi was the capital of the Vijayanagara Empire from 1336 to 1565 (as Vijayanagara), when it was abandoned. It was a fortified city. Chronicles left by Persian and European travellers, particularly the Portuguese, say that Hampi was a prosperous, wealthy and grand city near the Tungabhadra River, with numerous temples, farms and trading markets. Hampi-Vijayanagara is estimated to be the world's second-largest city by 1500, after Beijing, and probably India's richest at that time, attracting traders from Persia and Portugal. The Vijayanagara Empire was defeated by a coalition of Muslim sultanates; its capital was conquered, pillaged and destroyed by Muslim armies in 1565, after which Hampi remained in ruins.
Located in Karnataka near the small modern town of Hampi with the city of Hosapete 13 kilometres (8.1 miles) away, Hampi's ruins are spread over 4,100 hectares (16 sq mi) and it has been described by UNESCO as an "austere, grandiose site" of more than 1,600 surviving remains of the last great Hindu kingdom in South India that includes "forts, riverside features, royal and sacred complexes, temples, shrines, pillared halls, mandapas, memorial structures, water structures and others".

</text><timestamp>13.03.2025 20:22</timestamp></note></topic></data>